Guide to the Mariposa portrait series.
Mariposa portrait series.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Mariposa portrait series.
7602
Don Bachardy
12 items (1 folder).
Ink drawings.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Ink drawings by Don Bachardy of leaders of the gay and lesbian liberation movement.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Ink drawings by Don Bachardy of leaders of the gay and lesbian liberation movement, including Elaine Noble, Frank Kameny, Phyllis Lyon, Del Martin, Morris Kight, Charles F. Brydon, David Goodstein, James Foster, Barbara Gittings, Jean O'Leary, Reverend Troy Perry, and Bruce Voeller.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Bachardy, Don.; Brydon, Charles F.; Foster, James.; Gittings, Barbara.; Goodstein, David.; Kameny, Frank.; Kight, Morris.; Lyon, Phyllis.; Martin, Del.; Noble, Elaine.; O'Leary, Jean.; Perry, Troy.; Voeller, Bruce.; Mariposa Foundation.
Subjects:
Gay liberation movement.; Gay rights.; Gay men.; Lesbians.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Alternate Form of Material:
The portraits in the collection have been digitized and are accessible through the RMC image portal..
RELATED MATERIALS
Collecting Program: Human Sexuality Collection.
Charles F. Brydon's papers are at the Washington State Historical Society.
ITEM LIST
- Frank Kameny, October 3, 1980; REX023_018
- Elaine Noble, October 3, 1980; Elaine Noble won a seat in the Massachusetts House of Representatives in 1974. As the first openly LGBT candidate to win a state level election, she began a new era in electoral politics.; REX023_138
- Barbara Gittings, October 1, 1980; REX023_169
- Jean O'Leary, circa 1980-1984; Jean O'Leary, lesbian activist and co-founder of the National Gay Task Force; REX023_170
- Reverend Troy Perry, July 30, 1980; REX023_171
- James Foster, November 6, 1980; REX023_172
- Bruce Voeller, April 15, 1980; REX023_173
- Morris Kight, June 10, 1980; REX023_174
- David Goodstein, August 18, 1980; REX023_175
- Charles F. Brydon, October 2, 1980; REX023_176
- Phyllis Lyon, September 7, 1980; REX023_177
- Del Martin, September 7, 1980; REX023_178